And after all, we can also head over to the settings part of chat GPT.
So how we do that is by coming on our name and clicking and clicking settings.
We'll be able to head over to the settings of chat GPT.
So as you see, we have tabs over here.
We have general, which says appearance.
Appearance is about the color theme, so it can also be light, right?
As you see, this is the light mode of chat GPT.
And the default mode for a lot of you guys, but over here, as you see,
it is already set to system.
So it will use the system settings of the very device that you're using in order to detect your preferred color mode and color theme.
We also have accent color, so it's also setable over here.
We also have language, it's on auto detect, but we can set a specific language for the conversations that we have with the chat bot.
We also have spoken language, which is about the voice mode and stuff, you know?
And we also have this voice part, so we can choose among the voice actors, you know?
Choose the one that we want to talk about when we navigate to the voice mode.
We have these names over here, and by clicking itch and clicking play, you'll be able to see that a sample audio will be played for us.
Hey, it's great to meet you. How's your day going?
So as you see, this is working on some cool stuff together, right?
And yes, I set it back to Arbor, headed over to notifications.
We also can have settings for notifications, you know, it's obvious.
We also have personalization, custom instructions about you, you know, your name, your occupation.
So these will help you when it comes to getting better and more accurate results in the conversations that we have, and you have, which activity.
We have memory, so we can manage it.
We can go through all those things that chat GPD has memorized from us, and we can clear that history using this manage button.
We have apps and connectors.
We don't want to go through that right now, but GPT has also its own apps that you can set up on it.
We have data controls, and this one is for shared links, archived chats.
As you see, they are accessible over here, clicking manage.
We can archive all chats or delete all chats.
These are all available over here.
We can export data, and we also can probably import data, you know, when we're using a new account or something like that.
We also have security settings, so this is probably about your password, authenticator, you know, two step authentication, etc.
We have parental controls, so this is for the kids, when you're giving your, let's say, chat bot to your kid, and you want him or her to be safe.
You can come to parental control and set to do those settings over here.
We also have account, and after all, we have no more, right?
So here you can also upgrade using this button, as well as this button that was over here.